&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：最后一个话题是我们一直在跳舞
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So one kind of final
topic is we've been kind of dancing around
使用您的构建工具来帮助您的想法。
this idea of using your
build tools to help you.
我们的构建工具有很多好的方面和不好的方面。
And our build tools have a lot
of good things and bad things.
最棒的是它们是自动化的。
The best part is that they're automated.
贯穿始终，我们看到了Optimizely，它可以使用启发式来尝试可能的速度
Going through, we saw Optimizely which can
use the heuristics to try to maybe speed
提高你的代码。
up your code.
我们甚至看到Babble low Dash有能力进去
We even saw Babble low dash has
the ability to go in there and
做代码抖动，
do the code shaking,
树的摇动不会带来你不需要的低破折号的部分，对吗？
the tree shaking to not bring in parts
of low dash that you don't need right?
我们已经看到工具可以做很多这样的事情，很多时候如果你
We've seen that tools can do a lot of
these things, and a lot of times if you
可以自动化的东西，你会做得比你试图用手做得更好。
can automate something, you're gonna do it
better than if you try to do it by hand.
说服你的整个团队用手去做，永远不要搞砸，对吗？
Convince your entire team to do it
by hand and never mess up, right?
因此，有很多很好的工具可以做到这一点。
So there's a lot of great tools for that.
这个叫做Purify CSS，它真的很棒，因为它所做的就是它看起来
This one's called Purify CSS and it's
really great cuz what it does is it looks
就像你的CSS文件一样，它剥离了所有你实际上没有使用的CSS。
like your CSS file and it strips out all
the CSS that you're not actually using.
我们在Render ed Performance一节中谈到了这一点。
We talked about that in the render
ed performance section.
嘿，如果你有更少的CSS，你可以更快地进行选择器匹配。
Hey, if you have less CSS,
you can do the selector matching faster.
你可以通过手工对它进行微调，对吗？
You can go through and
fine-tune it by hand, right?
这是一个选择。
That's an option.
而且您可能会比这个工具做得更好，但是
And you'll probably do a better
job than this tool would, but
还有把事情搞砸的风险，事实上你必须这么做，
also the risk of messing it up,
the fact that you actually have to do it,
你必须保持它的最新的事实，对吗？
the fact you have to keep it up to date,
right?
有一些工具可以帮助我们。
There are tools that can kinda help us.